

JOSÉ JANTARADA

_

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is José. I'm a freelance graphic designer based in Porto, Portugal. My work reflects my journeys through the design, advertising, but most of all, life experiences.

I like everything where I can use my creativity to create new things, although I have a main focus on logo design, branding and identity. I'm passionate about typography and I believe in less is more, something you'll find in my portfolio. My designs characterize themselves by simplicity with a quirky twist.

If you have any ideas, projects or opportunities you'd like to discuss, please get in touch.

EDUCATION

LICENTIATE DEGREE

Communication Design ESAD / Escola Superior de Artes e Design Matosinhos, Portugal www.esad.pt 2006 - 2007

BACHELOR'S DEGREE

Communication Design ESAD / Escola Superior de Artes e Design Matosinhos, Portugal www.esad.pt 2003 - 2006

HIGHSCHOOL

Interactive Image (MULTIMEDIA)
IAI / Instituto das Artes e da Imagem
Porto, Portugal
www.iai.pt
2000 - 2003

CURRICULUM VITAE

GENERAL INFO

NAME

José Jantarada

NATIONALITY

Portuguese

LOCATION

Porto, Portugal

EDUCATION

Degree in Communication Design

CONTACTS

PHONE

+351 918 558 423

EMAIL

jose.jantarada@gmail.com

SKYPE

jose.jantarada

VIMEO

www.vimeo.com/josejantarada



PORTFOLIO

WEBSITE

www.josejantarada.ml

ADDITIONAL TRAINNING

ADVANCED PROFESSIONAL TRAINING COURSE

Motion Graphics (120 HOURS) AdC / Alquimia da Cor Porto, Portugal www.alquimiadacor.pt Feb. 2013 - May 2013

ADVANCED PROFESSIONAL TRAINING COURSE

Multimedia Producer (200 HOURS) AdC / Alquimia da Cor Porto, Portugal www.alquimiadacor.pt Jan. 2012 - May 2012

MODULAR TRAINING COURSE

Adobe FLASH (30 HOURS)
CFA'AD / Centro de Formação
Avançada em Artes e Design
Vila Nova de Gaia, Portugal
www.cfa-ad.com
Nov. 2009 - Dec. 2009

TYPOGRAPHY WORKSHOP

Tipocracia (10 HOURS)
ESAD / Escola Superior de Artes e Design
Matosinhos, Portugal
www.esad.pt
Oct. 2006

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE

Graphic Designer Porto, Portugal 2007 - Present

MURIS / COMMUNICATION GROUP

Graphic Designer Maia, Portugal www.muris.pt Apr. 2012 - Aug. 2013

ADEREÇO / BRAND ACTIVATION

Graphic Designer Porto, Portugal www.adereco.com Oct. 2008 - Jan. 2012

COLUNEX / TAILORED COMFORT

Graphic Designer / Traineeship Paredes, Portugal www.colunex.pt Mar. 2008 - Aug. 2008

M. SOUTINHO / ARCHITECTS

Graphic Designer
Vila Nova de Gaia, Portugal
www.msoutinhoarquitectos.com
Sep. 2007 - Feb. 2008

LANGUAGES

PORTUGUESE

Native

ENGLISH

Written ★★★☆☆
Spoken ★★★☆☆
Listening ★★★☆

SPANISH

Written ★★☆☆☆ Spoken ★★☆☆☆ Listening ★★★★☆

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Photoshop Illustrator **** InDesign **★★★☆☆** Affinity Designer ****** Dreamweaver (HTML/CSS) *** Animate (FLASH) **** After Effects *** Premiere **★★★☆☆** Final Cut ***** Google Analytics **** MS Office **** Windows/Mac

CLIENTS

Sogrape Wines, UDACA Wines, APICCAPS, Portuguese Shoes, IMPETUS, Associação Portuguesa da Cortiça, Auditório Serralves, Lavazza, Panike, Carglass, Ergovisão, Grupótico, Parque Nascente, Fórum Aveiro, Freixial Shopping, Ria Shopping, Ogentaly Seguros, VIRTUALP, iBrandit, Bascol Group, Sodecia Group, Cofanor, Laboratorios LETI, Omega Prisfar, Padimat, Associação Empresarial de Sintra, Mercal Consulting Group, Coren Group, Hotel Tryp Porto, Marina Club Lagos Resort, Angstrom, Associação Comercial do Distrito de Viseu, Eurotox, Valcontrol, Polisport.